Junya Wang

SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

I am a full-stack product designer with 8 years of experience crafting digital solutions for clients from innovative startups to Fortune 100 companies, by driving every step of the design process from stakeholder workshop, user research, user experience/interface design, to prototype, usability testing and iteration. My clients include: 3M, New York University, Barnes and Noble, Tempur-Pedic, ReadyRefresh, lululemon athletica, Vancity, etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Design Consultant, Deloitte, Freelance

Oct 2021 - Present · Remote

 Provided advice and guidance for the user experience and usability testing preparation for one of Deloitte's internal tools

Senior Product Designer, Cognizant Softvision

Apr 2019 - Present · Vancouver, Canada

- Led initial discovery workshops to help clients develop the best product strategy required to achieve their business and user experience goals
- Drove every step of the design process from initial product strategy, to user research, user experience/interface design, to prototype and usability testing
- Led the design team by defining realistic scope, providing design estimates and planning attainable timeline to ensure design deliverables are on schedule and with high standard
- Conducted in-person and remote user research and usability testings sessions to learn user behaviors, gain insights, validate assumptions and refine product strategy and user experience in an iterative approach
- Mentored other designers by providing guidance and support to help them grow faster

UX/UI Designer, Cognizant Softvision

Jul 2014 - Mar 2019 · Vancouver, Canada

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams and designed digital experience for mobile applications, web apps and smart table/mirror
- Researched and designed for AR/VR experience and presented my design process, learnings and outcomes to the entire company
- Initiated building and evolving design system for projects to create a shared and scalable design principle across teams

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University, BSc. Interactive Arts and Technology

2009 - 2014 · Vancouver, Canada

AYAJUNYA.COM

ayajunya@gmail.com +1 778 859 9861

COMPETENCIES

Product Design & Strategy Service Design Design System User Research/Testing AR/VR Design Inclusive Design Front-end Development

TOOLS

Figma, Sketch, Adobe CC, InVision, Zeplin, Miro, Mural, Lookback, Sublime

CERTIFICATES

Scrum.org

2021

Professional Scrum Master I Professional Scrum Product Owner I

Google

2020

Google Analytics for Beginner

AlterSpark

2019

Emotional Design Psychology Psychology for Digital Behavior Change

IDEO

2018

Human-Centered Service Design

Nielson Norman Group

2017

Becoming a UX Strategist